阿憨居然要我们打扫这间破餐厅
I can't believe Han is making us tidy up this damn diner.
这跟让妓女戴端庄的教堂帽一样
It's like putting a pretty church hat on a whore.
拜托 使劲 快点
Come on, harder, faster!
做再快点 再使劲点
Do it faster and harder.
这是阿憨对妓男爱力克湿的语录集吗
What is, "things Han says to a male hustler," Alex.
没时间开玩笑了 麦克斯
No time for jokes, Max.
卫生检查员很快就要到了
The health inspector will be here soon,
我一定要得到A级
and I need to get that "A" rating.
这件餐厅想拿到A级干净度评鉴
This diner getting an "A" for cleanliness
就跟我去买A罩杯胸罩一样不可能
would be like me getting an "A" for a bra size.
肯定能 我做得很彻底
Oh, it will happen. I did a thorough job.
他是料理铁人还是绝命毒师啊
Is he making omelets or crystal meth?
奥列格 你让阿憨给你戴上两个发网啊
Oleg, you let Han put you in two hair nets?
三个 还有一个我不想说在哪
Three. I don't want to talk about it.
抱歉迟到了 我刚做指甲耽搁了
Sorry I'm late. I was having my nails done.
这是两年来我第一次不用马不停蹄忙活
It's the first time I stopped moving in two years,
我居然睡着了
and I fell asleep.
你居然有钱去做指甲
You had money to get your nails done?
提问 做妓有你想象中那么糟吗
Question: Was prostitution as disgusting as you thought it would be?
阿憨出钱的啦
Han paid for it.
那就是比你想象中还惨
Oh, so it was worse.
你来啦
There she is.
我的镇店美人
There's my show pony.
让我看看你那玉手
Let me see them digits.
我要你当检查员进店后
I want you to be the first thing
第一眼见到的人事物
the health inspector sees when he enters.
你金发闪闪 整洁大方
You're just so blonde and clean.
那我呢 为何我啥好处都没有
Where's my manicure? How come I don't get anything?
哪可能忘了你的份 50块给你
Oh, I haven't forgotten you. Here's 50 bucks.
他来检查时 你待一边去
Beat it until the inspector leaves.
有人会觉得这是侮辱 但我只要求给75块
Some would be insulted. I'm gonna ask for $75.
妥了 给你吧
And, you are going to get it.
我有个好消息 在做指甲时
I have exciting news. At the nail salon,
我听说了一个很值得我们去的研讨会
I heard about this amazing seminar we should go to.
不要 不行 不许
Oh, no, no, no.
我去过一个研讨会
I went to a seminar once.
那次差点被三百个韩国人强娶
I was almost married to 300 Koreans.
这是给企业主参加的品牌研讨会
It's a branding seminar for business owners
讲如何搞清自己品牌的定位 并做好准备
to define who they are and get them primed and ready
等待机遇之窗的到来
for their window of opportunity.
我还宁愿我被三百韩国人强娶呢
I think I'd rather be married to 300 Koreans.
这样我就能随时做指甲了
Then I could get my nails done whenever I wanted.
麦克斯 这不是骗人的
Max, this is the real deal.
开研讨会的女人是品牌大师呢
The woman who runs it is a branding genius.
耐克的"做就对了"标语就是她的作品
She created the Nike "Just do it."
"做"就对了才不是她发明的呢
Oh, that woman didn't make up "Just do it."
这话被高中泡妞淫男们用了几百年了
High school boyfriends have been using that for centuries.
你怎么还没走
You're still here!
要给多少你才满意啊 再加10块如何
What's it gonna take, another $10?
我根本不需要参加研讨会
Hey, I don't need a seminar.
我发现我能致富的品牌了 "讨人厌"
I found a brand that's gonna get me rich: obnoxious!
厄尔 清理你收银台的进度如何了
Okay, Earl, how is cleaning your area coming along?
我发现不少陈年老纸巾
I've got decades of napkins over here
上面写满了我当年的奇思妙想
with all my old ideas on them.
看来纸巾就是当年的微博啊
Apparently, napkins were the old Twitter.
你好
Hello.
能告知店主
Could you tell the owner
卫生检查员到了吗
the health inspector has arrived?
原来您是女人
Oh, you are a woman.
真谢谢你看出来啊
Thank you for noticing.
你就是李憨吗
Are you Han Lee?
阿憨 这是...
Hey, Han, is this the...
那请问您想先从哪开始检查呢
So where would you like to start?
先从"男厕"开始吧
Sadly, the men's room.
核弹爆点级灾区
Ground zero.
我很快就来陪您
I will join you in a second.
先请问是萝特洛小姐还是太太
Is it Miss or Mrs. Rotello?
是小姐 谢谢你询问
It's Miss. Thank you for asking.
咱们厕所里见
I'll see you at the toilets.
重灾区现在感觉美好多了
Ground zero just got a lot nicer.
阿憨 检察员小姐好像是想"检查"你哦
Han, I think that health inspector wants to inspect you.
别乱说 她听见了 会给我个"F"的
Stop! If she hears you, she'll give me an "F."
她应该是想你"F"[操]她吧
I think she wants you to give her an "F."
麦克斯 我付你90块了 快走人
Max, I paid you $90. Now, go!
-给 麦克斯 -这是什么
- Here, Max. - What's this?
我们参加研讨会的六百块就靠这个赚了
That's how we'll make the $600 we need for the seminar.
我去金考打印店印了旧货拍卖传单
I made flyers for a yard sale at Kinko's.
哇 同一句话里说出"金考"跟"旧货拍卖"
Wow, "Kinko's" and "yard sale" in the same breath.
我内心是怎么强大到这地步的
Where do I keep finding this inner strength?
估计是苏菲带着要卖的旧货来了
That must be Sophie with her yard sale stuff.
姑娘们 你们好啊
Hi, girls!
苏菲 你的那些垃圾旧物[阴茎]呢
Hey, Sophie! Where's all your junk?
跟平常一样 放我后车厢里了[屁股]
Oh, where it always is, in my trunk!
你看这里
Well, look here.
这里面放了不少奥列格
I got a bunch of stuff that Oleg wanted
想捐给你们拍卖的东西
to donate to your yard sale.
他人真好
Aw, that's so nice of him.
他完全不知道这件事呢
Oh, yeah, he doesn't know about it.
这是他那些
Yeah, it's all the stuff
留在我家没拿走的东西
he's been leaving around my apartment.
他越来越没自觉 不懂分寸 所以...
He's getting way too comfortable, so...
统统卖了吧
Sell it all! Yeah.
他那本护照你估计可以卖个几块钱吧
You probably can get a couple of bucks for his passport.
他花八十块买的
Yeah, he paid $80 for it.
他把东西留下
Maybe he's leaving things around
很可能是因为想跟你再进一步啊
because he wants to take things to another level,
可能想搬来同居呢
maybe even move in.
闺蜜私语啊
Oh, girl talk.
你们不像电视上那样 先给我倒杯鸡尾酒吗
Shouldn't you serve me a cosmo like they do on television?
我们俩穷光蛋 家里没鸡尾酒
Don't have any cosmos, as we're broke
而且现在也不是1998年《欲望都市》热播的时候
and it's not 1998, but...
-要不来个粉红小蛋糕吧 -这个更好
- how about a pink cupcake? - Oh, even better.
奥列格都跟你表白过 说爱你了
Maybe now that Oleg has told you he loves you,
会不会是你对亲密关系有恐惧症呢
you're starting to have intimacy issues about getting close.
拜托哦
Oh, come on.
这种废话你留着废物拍卖会卖吧
Save that garbage for your yard sale.
那家伙就是太常在楼上了
Yeah, the man is just up there too much.
虽然他在楼上时都在我"下面" 但...
I mean, he's down there when he's up there, but, yeah...
但他真的太常来了
It's way too much, yeah.
他得改改 不然就得滚
He's got to change, or he's out.
麦克斯 谢谢你的小蛋糕
Hey, thanks for the cupcake, Max.
卡洛琳
And, Caroline...
我不知道你有啥贡献 随便啦
I don't know what you add, but, yeah.
我们的旧货拍卖还没布置好
Our yard sale is not quite all set up yet.
你来早了 传单说下午一点到五点
You're Early. Our flyer said 1:00 to 5:00.
我讨厌传单
Oh, I don't do flyers.
特鲁迪小姐 我的名片
Miss Trudy, my card.
她是我老婆 特鲁迪小姐
This is my wife, Miss Trudy,
而这鸟的名字叫斯考特
and the bird's name is Scott.
丹尼斯·恩迪克特三世
Dennis Endicott the third,
旧货店寻宝员与布鲁克林疯狂媚俗艺术天才
Thrift shop scout and Brooklyn's crazy kitsch genius.
"万物之王"[改编自《魔戒》]
"Lord of the things."
我们有很多古典文化物品
So, I have lots of classic couture pieces.
您绝对不会失望
You won't be disappointed.
我们失望过了 特鲁迪小姐 你说说
Well, I have been before. Miss Trudy?
我们大老远跑去宾州
We went all the way to Pennsylvania for
参加电视剧《生命的事实》投沙包游戏
a Facts of Life bean bag toss game.
布莱儿居然不在啊 布莱儿
No Blair! No Blair.
就去了两个托蒂家的小角色
Just two Tooties.
老天有时就他妈爱捉弄人
Life just sucks it hard sometimes.
对吧 斯考特
Am I right, Scott?
那边椅子上都是我的东西
So, on that chair are my things,
你会发现里面有很多...
and you'll notice that there's a lot
我发现了 14 全收了
Oh, I already did. 14 for all of it.
1400块吗 没问题
$1,400, perfect!
什么1400块 宝贝 是14快
Hundred? Darling, $14.
这些都是复古玩意呢
But this is all vintage.
是复古 还是过季而已啊
Vintage, or just out of season?
等等 那是鸡块宝宝吗
Wait, is that a nugget buddy?
特鲁迪小姐 他们有鸡块宝宝牛仔版
Miss Trudy, they have the cowboy.
他爱死那个了
He loves the cowboy.
必须的
I bet he does.
我松了好大一口气
Oh, I am so relieved.
每次我们没淘到什么好宝贝 他会很生气
When we don't find anything good, he gets really mad...
我就遭殃了
at me.
抱歉 那个是不小心放出来的
I'm sorry, that's not supposed to be out.
我不想拆了那组玩具
I can't break up the set.
你十个鸡块宝宝全有吗
You have all ten nugget buddies?
以及1993年至今每个开心乐园餐玩具
Yep, and every other happy meal toy since 1993.
我妈以前整天带我去麦当劳
My mom used to take me there a lot.
也常常就把我丢在麦当劳 都一样啦
Well, she used to leave me there a lot, but same diff.
-六百块买你那一组 -成交
- $600 for the whole collection. - Sold!
不不 才不卖呢
Whoa, whoa, not sold.
卖了吧 这关系到我们未来呢
Max, come on, this is our future.
那还是我的过去呢 不卖
Well, those are my past. No sale.
咱们走 斯考特
Let's go, Scott.
"托蒂门"事件又重演了
This is "Tootiegate" all over again.
还有你
And you
我们回家后 你最好快点戴上打屁屁枕头
when we get home, you better put on the punishment pillow.
别担心 我就好这口
Don't worry. I kind of like it.
这下子戴帽子的马
Well, so much for a horse in a hat
都不再是这里最怪的一件事了
being the weirdest thing in this yard.
再跟我解释一次
Explain to me again
一个我两年前花三千块买的东西
how an item I paid $3,000 for just two years ago
现在比一个
is worth less than something
有沾酱的东西还便宜
that came with a dipping sauce!
开心乐园餐的玩具能唤起人们当年的美好
A happy meal toy reminds people of a sweeter time,
那是个单纯美好 没卡戴珊的时代
a simpler time, a pre-Kardashian time.
注意 注意
Attention, attention!
我有份很重要的文件公布
I have something very important here.
你的DNA检验报告 证实你妈是个亚洲人
The results of your DNA test proving your mother was asian
而你爸是个松果吗
and your father was a pine nut?
不是 是我们拿到了
No, we got our letter grade
城市卫生检查处的评分了
from the city health inspector's office.
哇 我们拿了"B"
Whoo! We got a "B"!
这是我这辈子第一次
That's the first "B" I ever got
不用靠跟人舌吻得的"B"呢
I didn't have to French kiss for.
才"B" 惨了 惨了
A "B"? No, no, no, no!
我这人可不能得个"B"
This boy don't play with no Bs.
我要打给那个叫珍·萝特洛的臭娘们理论
I'm calling that little tease, Miss Jean Rotello, right now.
这下惨了 亚洲人接受不了得"B"
This isn't good. Asians don't do well with Bs.
我在沃顿那会 有一次我得了"B"
At Wharton, I got a "B," and the Japanese kid
坐我隔壁的日本人去自尽了呢
who sat next to me killed himself.
奥列格 我都开始习惯你这打扮了
Oleg, I'm kind of getting used to this look now.
你看起来就像本·拉登的鬼魂
You kind of look like Bin Laden's ghost.
晚安 女孩们
Good night, girls.
我要去苏菲家过夜了
I'm going to go over and spend the night at Sophie's.
还是别去吧
No, maybe not.
你为何这么说
Why would you say that?
因为她这人废话多
Because she can't stop herself.
只是她有时候也会想要私人空间吧
It's just, she might like a little space sometimes.
她想要私人空间 她说的吗
She needs space? Did she say that?
也不是这么说的啦
Not in so many words.
她就是这么说的啊
No, those were the words.
苏菲很喜欢有你的陪伴
Look, Sophie loves having you around.
只是她说她觉得你有点
It's just, she told us that you're getting
越来越没自觉 不懂分寸 这些是她在
a little too comfortable there when she came over
拿你东西给我们拍卖的时候说的
to sell all your stuff at our yard sale.
-我知道这话听了有点... -但你还是说个不停
- I know how that sounds- - And yet, you keep going.
奥列格 苏菲只是觉得有点要窒息了
Oleg, Sophie is just feeling a little smothered.
她还觉得快窒息呢
She feels smothered?
你试过跟她的胸器玩"泰胸压脸"吗
Have you ever tried motorboating those cans of hers?
有过一次 但那次是我喝太醉了
Once, but I was very drunk at the time.
你就稍微改变一下嘛
Just make a few changes,
一切又会恢复原样的
and everything will be right back on track.
你最好闭嘴
And stop talking now.
做一点改变 我一直都在为她改变
Make some changes? That's all I've done for her.
我改变了我的家具 改变我的习惯
I changed my furniture, I changed my ways.
还改成了不到一周就换一次内裤呢
I changed my underwear more than once a week.
够了 不再为阿憨改变
That's it. No more changing for Han...
也不再为苏菲改变
and no more changing for Sophie.
我受够做改变了 本淫王要回归了
I'm done changing. I'm back, baby.
请把消息传遍天下
Spread the word!
他要"传遍天下"的不只是消息而已吧
I think he's gonna be spreading more than the word.
老子想杀人
I want to kill someone!
为什么 你看的迪士尼儿童喜剧被砍了吗
Why, did they cancel Suite Life of Zack and Cody?
不 我刚跟餐厅卫生检查员打完电话
No, I just got off the phone with the restaurant inspector
她这么晚还接你的电话啊
She answered her phone at this time of night?
拜托 她这种老姑婆晚上也只能待在家
Come on, it's not like she was out on the town.
阿憨
Han!
我觉得你手里拿着那个"B" 应该是"贱B"的意思
I think that "B" you're holding might stand for "bitch."
她居然告诉我 我得了个"B"是因为
And she told me I got a "B" because of the conditions
洗碗区后面的密室环境不佳
of the back room off the dishwasher area.
我甚至不知道我们有个密室 你们知道吗
I didn't even know we had a back room, did you?
不知道 但在这个价值观被颠倒的世界
No, but of course there's a mysterious back room
当然会有一个神秘的密室
in this new upside down world,
那里芝士是市长
where a piece of cheese is mayor
而大牌DKNY的创始人则是无名小卒
and Donna Karan is a no one!
就是这里
Oh, there it is.
我一直以为这属于
I always thought that was the property
隔壁酒吧的地方
of the bar next door.
如果我们跟酒吧共用一扇门
If we share a door with a bar,
那我的休息时间要变得更长更醉了
my breaks are about to get longer and drunker.
姑娘们你们一边等着 我来把这架子推开
Wait here, girls, while I push this rack away.
健身了这么久 是时候大展身手了
P90x, don't fail me now!
我的灵魂看起来一定跟这房间一样
I'm pretty sure this is what my soul looks like.
为了我的"A" 现在我得请一个抢清队
Now I'm going to have to hire an emergency crew to come
在周五前帮我把这弄干净
clean this by friday to get my "A."
靠
Oh, damn it.
我和卡洛琳就可以做 好吗
I guess Caroline and I can do it.
你疯了吗 麦克斯 我可做不了
Are you insane? Max, I can't.
我又不像你 在铁路上干过力气活
I haven't worked on the railroads like you.
拜托
Come on.
阿憨需要一个"A"
Han needs his "A,"
我们需要钱参加研讨会
and we need the money for that seminar.
这难道不是传说中的"机遇之窗"吗
Isn't this one of those "windows of opportunity"?
-六百块 -算了吧 姑娘们
- $600. - Forget it, girls.
瞧瞧这些墙壁
Look at these walls.
我需要专业的蒸汽清洁人员
I need professional steam cleaners.
我以前有用蒸汽清洁过东西啊
I have steam cleaned before.
不然租来的舞会礼服上的麦芽酒
I mean, how else do you get malt liquor and blood stains
和初夜的血渍怎么弄掉呀
out of a rented prom dress?
这里面又潮又湿
Ugh, it's so humid and damp in here.
现在我总算明白蛋蛋的感受了
Now I know how balls feel.
我把这电线弄走吧
Let me just move this cord out of
我刚被电到[吓到]了
Oh! I just got a shock!
错
No.
你回家发现你妈跟你十年级的心动对象
A shock is coming home to find your mom
一起泡澡时 才是真正的吓死人
in the tub with your tenthgrade crush.
我应该把这些电线塞回去...
I should push these light cords back up over...
是个蟑螂窝
Uh, it's a roach nest.
没事的 没事的 没事的啦
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay!
真的没事啦
It's okay!
好消息 那些蟑螂都死了
Good news, they're already dead.
坏消息是 当我把它们从你头发抓出来时
Bad news, as I pull them out of your hair,
它们的尸体正在腐烂
they're decomposing.
你是在哭吗
Are you crying?
我做不来
I can't do this.
即使为了研讨会也不行
Not even for the seminar.
那我把我的开心乐园餐玩具卖掉吧
I'll sell my happy meals.
麦克斯 你没必要这么做
Max, you don't have to do that.
-但我们需要这笔钱 -好的 太棒了
- But we need the money. - Okay, great!
鸡块宝宝
Hey, nugget buddies.
那个带着鸟的男人一到这里
As soon as the man with the bird gets here,
你们将离开我的悉心照料
you'll be leaving my loving care
进入一个巨大而险恶的世界
and going out into the big, bad world.
鞋子会践踏你们
Shoes will step on you,
孩子会把你们绑在鞭炮上
kids will tie you to firecrackers,
某些神经病会把你们塞进卡车里
And some real sickos may even stick you in a truck
开车把你们带离这个州
and drive you across state line.
苏菲
Hi, Sophie.
奥列格背着我乱搞 老娘气疯了
Oleg cheated on me, and I'm so maaad!
我要砸东西发泄
Oh, I have to break things!
但我楼上公寓的所有东西都太好了
But everything upstairs in my apartment is too nice!
所以姑娘们 记得记账
So...run a tab, girls!
我还要继续砸
I gotta break more things!
住手 别砸那个箱子 那是我的开心...
Wait, don't break that box! That's my happy...
感觉好多了
I feel better.
真的
I really do.
好的 我走了
Okay. All right.
我觉得我们刚才看到的场面
I think we just saw what it would look like
就像绿巨人遭人背叛了一样
if someone cheated on the Incredible Hulk.
姑娘们
Hey, girls.
浪后苏菲回来了 请把消息传遍天下
Sophie's back. Spread the word!
麦克斯 瞧你的开心乐园餐玩具
Max, look, your happy meal toys.
我知道你因为玩具的事不开心 麦克斯
Look, I know you're upset about your toys, Max,
但你瞧 现在也挺好玩的呀
but come on, it's kind of fun.
在凌晨3点
There is only one kind of wet
只有一种"湿"的状态
that I have been at 3:00 in the morning
会让我觉得"好玩"
that I would call "Fun."
而这种恰恰不是
This is not it!
瞧 原来报纸盖住的
Oh, look! Under the newspaper,
是某种彩色玻璃窗
there's some sort of stained glass window there.
真漂亮
Aw, pretty!
你终于得到你想要的那笔钱
Oh, you're finally getting the money you wanted
你真是个奇葩
and you're so chipper.
用你的话说 我是"奇葩"
I'm "Chipper," to use your word,
是因为我们现在干活是为了挣钱
because we're working to earn money
让我们的品牌更上一层楼
to move our business brand forward.
别再说什么"品牌"了
Stop saying "Brand."
这个"研讨会"最好值回票价
And this "Seminar" better be worth it.
你干嘛用这种语气说话
Why are you saying it like that?
故意强调"研讨会"这个词
"Seminar," with quotes around it,
好像这是个蠢主意或什么的
like it's a silly idea or something.
我没有故意加重语气说"研讨会"
I didn't say "seminar" with quotes around it.
明明有 你说...
You did. You said
对不起
Ooh! Ooh, sorry!
Sorry!
我刚是想说明你的确有加重语气
I was trying to illustrate that you put quotes around it.
我累得要死 没力气加重语气
I am too tired to put quotes around things,
如果如果我要给某个词加重语气
but if I were gonna put quotes on a word,
那个词一定是"研讨会"
that word would be, "seminar"!
对了 还有"打造品牌"
Oh, and "branding"!
我会特意大大加重语气在
And I would put big, giant, dumbass quotes around
"打造品牌研讨会"这个词上
"branding seminar"!
麦克斯 你是故意的
Max, you did that on purpose!
或是这只是个意外
Oh, maybe it was just an accident!
住手 住手 你喷到电灯泡了
Stop! Stop! You're spraying the light cord!
喂 水和电"不是"
Hello! Water and electricity,
电死人的最佳组合吗
not the best combo!
正如我能想到的其他烂组合
Like some other not great combos I can think of.
我们吗 你是指我们吗
Us? You mean us?
怎么 现在我们不是最佳组合了吗
What, now we are not a great combo?
抱歉我建议我们去参加一个所谓的"研讨会"
Sorry I suggested we go to a quote-seminar-unquote.
抱歉我试图让我们更上一层楼
Sorry I'm trying to move us forward.
抱歉你觉得自己什么都会做
Sorry that you think you know how to do everything.
抱歉你不愿承认我会做生意的这一事实
Sorry that you resent the fact that I know how to do business.
抱歉你觉得自己很会做生意
Sorry that you think you know how to do business,
或者这就是我们第一家店倒闭的原因
and maybe that's why our first business failed.
抱歉你每天的休息两次去抽大麻
Sorry that you took two weed breaks every single day
而不是打电话招揽生意
instead of making work calls,
或者这才是我们蛋糕店倒闭的原因
And maybe that's why our business failed.
抱歉我没有多休息多抽大麻
Sorry that I didn't take more weed breaks,
因为我觉得跟你这种自称无所不知的人工作
because I really could have used them working with
真的很需要麻痹自己
a know-it-all like you!
抱歉该轮到我指责你了
And sorry it's my turn!
不 抱歉你对奥列格和苏菲的私事
No! Sorry that you, also, had to stick your nose
多管闲事
into Oleg and Sophie's business,
搞得现在男的劈腿 女的抓狂
So that he cheated, and she got mad and then,
经过一连串不可否认的直接作用
by an almost irrefutable line of direct action,
你害死了我的玩具
you killed my toys!
抱歉无论之前我是否做对过多少事情
Sorry that it doesn't matter how many things I ever did right
只要麦克斯开心乐园儿童餐的
because poor itty-bitty baby
可怜小玩具全碎了 我就是错的
Max's happy meal toys got all broked!
别逼我 麦克斯
Don't push me, Max!
你不是打造品牌的粉丝吗
You're such a fan of branding,
"做就对了"[耐克广告语]
"Just do it."
"按你想做的去做"[汉堡王广告语]
"Have it your way."
"拉斯维加斯输的钱 就留在拉斯维加斯吧"
"What happens in vegas, stays in vegas."
"有喝牛奶了吗"
"Got milk?"
有想到其他白痴的生意标语吗
Got any other stupid business ideas?
住手
Stop!
住手 住手 快住手
Stop, stop, stop it, stop it!
我受够了
I am done!
不 我才受够了
No, I'm done!
不 我们都受够了
No, we're both done!
好 咱们俩都受够了
Fine, we're both done!
-受够了 -我也是
- Done! - Done!
不 我是真的受够了 麦克斯
No, I'm really done, Max!
我厌倦了努力让梦想成真
I'm tired of trying to make things happen!
我厌倦了逼着我们开蛋糕店
I'm tired of pushing us into cupcake shops!
我也厌倦了你逼着我们开蛋糕店
And I'm tired of you pushing us into cupcake shops too.
我们本来就没能力花钱开店
Shops that we couldn't afford in the first place.
天啊 天啊 麦克斯
Oh, my God! Oh, my God, Max!
麦克斯 你没事吧
Max, are you all right?
心肺复苏 是怎么做的来着
CPR, what is it?
捏住她鼻子 然后往她嘴里吹气吗
Do you do pinch the nose and breathe into the mouth?
慢着慢着
Wait, wait!
我觉得应该先按压胸部
I think you're supposed to pump the chest first.
我永远都不可能翻越这两座"大山"
Well, I'll never get through those!
麦克斯 我要跟你嘴对嘴了
Max, I'm about to put my mouth on yours,
所以如果你不是闹着玩 那你最好现在醒来
so if you're kidding you better wake up right now.
麦克斯 求你别死
Max, please don't die.
求你别死 你是我最好的朋友
Please don't die. You're my best friend.
坐起来 坐起来
Sit up! Sit up, sit up!
-你没事吧 -发生什么事了
- Are you all right? - What happened?
你刚抓到电线
You grabbed that wire,
应该是触电了
and I think you got a little electrocuted.
我一直觉得我会被电
I always knew I'd be electrocuted,
但我以为会是在电椅[死刑]上
I just thought it would be in the chair.
天啊 我热死了 我需要新鲜空气
God, I'm so hot. I need air.
来这里 这边有窗 来
Come here. The window, come on.
来 来 到这里
Come on. Come on, over here.
这里 跪着 打开了
Here, kneel. Open!
靠 还有护窗板
Oh, damn, there are shutters.
我来弄开 你抓住墙
Here, hold on to the wall while I get this.
你没事吧 深呼一口气
Are you okay? Take a deep breath in.
吸气
Breathe in.
麦克斯 刚才太吓人了
Max, that was so scary.
有那么一瞬间 我以为你死了
For a second, I thought you died.
真可能呢 我记得看到一个满是火焰的地方
Maybe I did, 'cause I kind of remember a place with flames.
然后你在跟我亲热
and you were making out with me.
什么味道这么香
What is that delicious smell?
隔壁酒吧旁的披萨店
The pizza place next to the bar next door.
天啊 披萨的味道有这么好闻过吗
Oh, God, has a pizza ever smelled so good?
你们俩在干嘛
Hey, what are you guys doing?
这里是商店还是什么吗
Is that, like, a store or something?
-不是 -真可惜
- No. - Holler.
慢着 卡洛琳
Wait, Caroline...
这就是我们的"机遇之窗"
This is our window of opportunity!
麦克斯 这个主意太棒了
Max, what a great idea!
蛋糕外卖窗口 你就是个天才
A cupcake walk-up window? You're a genius!
我死而复生之后 可能变聪明了
I just might be since I died!
费用少太多了
So much less overhead.
这次我们从底层做起
And this time we'll be starting at the bottom,
我们不能往下走 只能往上爬
so we'll have nowhere to go but up.
谢天谢地
Thank God!
在底层的感觉真是舒服太多了
I am so much more comfortable at the bottom!
我心里有一种异样的感觉
Hey, I have this weird feeling inside.
我就是开心乐园餐
I'm Mchappy.
姑娘们
Hey, girls.
像阿姆斯特丹的妓女那样 在橱窗里服务吗
Turning tricks in a window like they do in Amsterdam?
不 我们刚发现了新的生意机会
No, we think we found our new business.
苏菲 这里是新的麦克斯自制小蛋糕店
Sophie, this is the new Max's homemade cupcakes.
说到窗户 那是奥列格的车吧
Speaking of windows, that's Oleg's car, right?
太好了
Yeah. Yeah.
有人打开机遇之窗
Well, some people open windows,
有人砸烂车窗
some people smash them.